Who are you?
She looks familiar.
I've seen her
somewhere before.
Wait, was it at the
Knights' stadium?
I'm Ted's girlfriend.
So you're the girl
Ted's been
telling me about.
He said you
were beautiful.
He wasn't exaggerating.
That's very
kind of you.
Beauty and
the beast, huh?
I don't understand
what you see in him.
The guy's a cripple.
He can't even
afford a decent gift.
You think our
gifts are cheap?
Why don't you
show us
something better?
Well,
I didn't have
much time
to prepare, but...
I pulled a little
something from
my own collection.
Hopefully Grandpa
doesn't mind.
Oh, from your
"collection", huh?
You sure it's
not some junk
you brought
from the attic?
So hurry up
and show us
what kind of
trash you brought.
Nothing extravagant,
just a painting.
A painting? Please.
How expensive
could that be?
It's Picasso's
Weeping Woman.
Worth around three
million dollars.